loftek.us 2015-12-26

# Loftek | Privacy Policy

## Coupon codes on www.amazon.com/loftek

  * $3.00 Off [DRG98PWF](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B009YP7Y56/)

  * $2.00 Off [EJQJFTEK](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00GLOHJAS/)

  * $3.00 Off [MYFE53XM](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B005XU7OL0/)

  * $4.00 Off [LLLTTAC5](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00GOJDB8O/)

  * $2.00 Off [EIZI8YVC](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00PBWGLDW/)

  * $2.00 Off [FHQ6QFTO](http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00OQ1CA6G)

###  Welcome to LOFTEK! Start your first order with a coupon code！

We highly appreciate all your reviews and suggestions! Our goal is to provide the best products and the best service to all our customers! For more exciting deals and free trial activities, please pay close attention to LOFTEK official website and Facebook @LOFTEK! If you have any problems, please feel free to contact us!

#####  Sincerely  
Your LOFTEK

Register your amazon account on amazon.com, add these products to cart.   
Enter corresponding codes at Check out.

1\. What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

2\. What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

3\. How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.   
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below

www.loftek.us  
techsupport@loftek.us  
1-480-330-3804
